AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IIIa: Organizing, 1918-1954
  - Columbia, Newberry and Laurens Railroad, 1922-1939 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-191; Oct. 24, 1922 - Jun. 15, 1939
  - Pere Marquette Railway, 1923-1934 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-192, pt. 1; Jul. 24, 1923 - Nov. 9, 1934
  - Grand Trunk Railway, 1923-1934 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-193; Nov. 12, 1923 - Jan. 23, 1934
  - Pittsburg and Shawmut Railroad, 1923-1941 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-194; Oct. 20, 1923 - Jun 13, 1941
  - San Antonio, Uvalde and Gulf Railroad, 1924-1939 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-195; Mar. 22, 1924 - Oct. 10, 1939
  - Missouri, Oklahoma and Gulf Railroad, 1923-1930 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-196; Oct. 22, 1923 - Feb. 1, 1930
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1924-1932 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-197, pt. 1; May 23, 1924 - Apr. 12, 1932
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-197, pt. 2; Jul 5, 1933 - Sept. 28, 1934
  - Detroit and Mackinac Railroad, 1923-1943 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-199; Jun. 4, 1923 - May 4, 1943
  - Washington Terminal Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-202; Oct. 30, 1923 - Oct. 19, 1934
  - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient Railway Company consolidated with Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, 1928-1929 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-203; Jan. 14, 1928 - Sept. 14, 1929
  - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient Railway Company consolidated with Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-203, pt. 2; Jan. 2, 1936 - Apr. 29, 1937
  - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient Railway Company consolidated with Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-203, pt. 3; May 1, 1937 - Sept. 29, 1937
  - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient Railway Company consolidated with Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, 1937-1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-203, pt. 4; Oct. 1, 1937 - Mar. 30, 1943
  - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1932-1935 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-204, pt. 2; Jan. 3, 1932 - Jan. 20, 1935
  - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1925-1937 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-205; Dec. 11, 1925 - Jul. 20, 1937
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad, 1923-1935 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-206; Dec. 30, 1923 - Sept. 24, 1935
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-207; Dec. 18, 1923 - Jul. 26, 1934
  - Central of Georgia, 1924-1934 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-208; Jan. 7, 1924 - Aug. 16, 1934
  - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad, 1928-1934 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-209; Apr. 27, 1928 - Sept. 26, 1934
  - Denver and Rio Grande Railroad, 1923-1936 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-210; May 25, 1923 - Feb. 13, 1936
  - Kansas City Terminal Railroad, 1930-1934 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-211; Feb. 1, 1930 - Nov. 27, 1934
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1922-1933 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-212, pt. 1; May 26, 1922 - Oct. 3, 1933
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1935-1938 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-212, pt. 2; Feb. 12, 1935 - Nov. 14, 1938
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-212, pt. 3; Nov. 22, 1938 - Dec. 29, 1939
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1939-1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-212, pt. 4; Dec. 29, 1939 - Jan. 29, 1947
  - Lake Erie and Western Railroad, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-213; May 20, 1925 - May 25, 1925
  - Long Island Railroad, 1931-1935 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-214; Jan. 23, 1931 - Jul. 9, 1935
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-215, pt. 1; Jan. 24, 1923 - Aug. 1, 1934
  - Rutland Railroad, 1923-1937 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-216; Dec. 29, 1923 - Jun. 15, 1937
  - Frisco Railroad, 1933-1942 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-217, pt. 1; Sept. 1, 1933 - Jul. 25, 1942
  - Frisco Railroad, 1935-1939 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-217, Consol.; Aug. 21, 1935 - Aug. 22, 1939
  - Frisco Mailing List (St. Louis and San Francisco), 1937 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-217; Feb. 1937 - Nov. 22, 1937
  - Frisco Mailing List (St. Louis and San Francisco), 1935-1937 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-217-23; Jan. 17, 1935 - Sept. 29, 1937
  - Wabash Railroad, 1929-1935 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-218, pt. 1-3; Dec. 11, 1929 - Dec. 30, 1935
  - Wabash Railroad, 1936-1942 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-218, pt. 4; Jan. 9, 1936 - Mar. 26, 1942
  - Wabash Railroad - Special, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-218; Oct. 5, 1933-Oct. 12, 1933
  - Pullman Organizing Campaign, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-219; Feb. 4, 1922 - Jul. 21, 1922
  - Pullman Organizing Campaign, 1934-1945 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-219, pt. 2; Aug. 23, 1934 - Sept. 27, 1945
  - Pullman Organizing Campaign, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-219; Mar. 22, 1946; Original list of employees who signed authorization cards
  - Pullman Organizing Campaign, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-219; Mar. 22, 1946; Extra list (incomplete) of employees as sent with invocation
  - Seaboard Airline Railway, 1923-1935 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Code No. 8-222; Sept. 15, 1923 - Feb. 8, 1935
  - Indianapolis Union Railroad, 1923-1937 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-223; Dec. 7, 1923 - Aug. 23, 1937
  - Indianapolis Union Railroad, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-223, Consol.; Jan. 29, 1936
  - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railroad, 1924-1933 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-226; Apr. 25, 1924 - Oct. 13, 1933
  - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-227; Aug. 1, 1929 - Dec. 27, 1929
  - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad, 1929-1940 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-227, pt. 2; Dec. 31, 1929 - Nov. 1, 1940
  - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-228; Dec. 6, 1923 - Feb. 27, 1934
  - Duluth and Iron Range Railroad, 1923-1932 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-230; Dec. 6, 1923 - Mar. 7, 1932
  - Duluth, Missabe and Northern Railroad, 1923-1937 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-231; Dec. 10, 1923 - Jun. 17, 1937
  - Midland Valley Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-232; Dec. 8, 1923 - Sept. 5, 1934
  - Hudson and Manhattan Railroad, 1921-1933 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-234; Jan. 20, 1921 - Nov. 14, 1933
  - St. Louis Refrigerator Car Railroad, 1923-1937 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-235; Dec. 5, 1923 - Apr. 12, 1937
  - Detroit, Toledo and Shoreline Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-236; Dec. 12, 1923 - Feb. 1934
  - Colorado, Wyoming and Eastern Railroad, 1923-1946 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-237; May 19, 1923 - Jan. 17, 1946
  - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1923-1930 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Code No. 8-238; Jan. 4, 1923 - Feb. 7, 1930
  - Peoria and Peken Union Railroad, 1924-1940 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Code No. 8-242; Jan. 9, 1924 - Mar. 25, 1940
  - Atlanta and West Point and Western Alabama Railroad, 1924-1934 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Code No. 8-243; Mar. 25, 1924 - Sept. 21, 1934
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1924-1942 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Code No. 8-244; Jan. 9, 1924 - Jul. 16, 1942
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railroad, 1924-1934 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Code No. 8-245; Jan. 15, 1924 - Dec. 19, 1934
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac, 1924-1937 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Code No. 8-246; Jan. 24, 1924 - Nov. 2, 1937
  - San Diego and Arizona Railway, 1923-1935 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Code No. 8-248; Mar. 16, 1923 - Nov. 23, 1935
  - Alabama and Vicksburg Railway & Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railway, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Code No. 8-251; Jan. 22, 1935
  - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad, 1934-1946 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Code No. 8-254; Jan. 19, 1934 - May 14, 1946
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific, 1924-1934 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Code No. 8-255; Mar. 19, 1924 - Nov. 28, 1934
  - Rock Island Railroad, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Code No. 8-257a; Sept. 29, 1925 - Nov. 13, 1925
  - Rock Island Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Code No. 8-257; Aug. 29, 1933 - Jul. 20, 1934
  - Rock Island Railroad, 1935-1943 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Code No. 8-257, pt. 7; Sept. 18, 1935 - Jul. 30, 1943
  - Staten Island Railroad, 1924-1932 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Code No. 8-259; May 15, 1924 - Sept. 19, 1932
  - Big Four (Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway(, 1924-1934 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Code No. 8-260; June 2, 1924 - Nov. 28, 1934
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1924-1935 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Code No. 8-261; Nov. 5, 1924 - Apr. 10, 1935
  - Tennessee Central Railroad, 1925-1933 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-265; Jan. 12, 1925 - Oct. 18, 1933
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-266; Mar. 23, 1929 - Nov. 20, 1929
  - Soo Line Railroad, 1924-1935 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-267; Jun. 2, 1924 - Feb. 18, 1935
  - Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburgh Railroad, 1925-1934 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-268; Feb. 28, 1925 - Dec. 18, 1934
  - Western Maryland Railway, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-270, pt. 1; Nov. 24, 1933 - Aug. 14, 1934
  - Western Maryland Railway, 1941-1946 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-270, pt. 2; Jan. 28, 1941 - Mar. 22, 1946
  - Pennsy Organizer, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Pennsy Organizer, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Pennsy Organizer, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1928-1946 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 1-9; Nov. 3, 1928 - Mar. 29, 1946
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 10; Apr. 29, 1946 - Nov. 13, 1946
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 11; Nov. 13, 1946 - Nov. 15, 1948
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 12; Jan. 21, 1949 - Nov. 17, 1949
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 13; Nov. 21, 1949 - May 31, 1951
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Expenses, 1938-1948 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 1; Dec. 22, 1938 - Apr. 20, 1948
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Expenses, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 2; Apr. 20, 1948 - Aug. 31, 1949
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Expenses, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 3; Aug. 30, 1949 - Dec. 30, 1949
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Expenses, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 4; Jan. 3, 1950 - Aug. 31, 1950
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Expenses, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-271, pt. 5; Aug. 30, 1950 - Jun. 29, 1951
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - M. Delancey, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Mar. 31, 1949 - Dec. 1, 1949
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Brotherhood of Railroad Shop Crafts of America, 1946-1951 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Nov. 9, 1946 - Dec. 5, 1951
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Campaign Expenses, 1944-1950 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Aug. 22, 1944 - Jun. 5, 1950
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - R.J. Hoolahan, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; May 7, 1951 - Sept. 26, 1951
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - E.F. Fountain, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Dec. 5, 1949 - Dec. 5, 1951
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - R.B. Stewart, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Nov. 8, 1949 - Nov. 22, 1949
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - C.W. Woomer, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Apr. 24, 1950 - Jun. 20, 1950
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - M.F. McGreevey, 1949-1952 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Jun. 26, 1949 - Jan. 23, 1952
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Geo. H. Akers, 1948-1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; May 1, 1948 - May 1, 1950
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - R.D. Award, 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Code No. 8-271, exp.; Feb. 3, 1948 - Jan. 28, 1952
  - Atlanta Joint Organizing Committee, 1925-1938 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-273; May 26, 1925 - Sept. 24, 1938
  - Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad, 1925-1934 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-274; Oct. 19, 1925 - Feb. 7, 1934
  - Chicago Great Western Railroad, 1925-1934 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-275; Dec. 14, 1925 - Sept. 24, 1934
  - Peoria-Eastern Railway, 1926-1940 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-276; Feb. 2, 1926 - Feb. 8, 1940
  - American Federation of Labor General Organizer, 1930-1927 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-277; Apr. 21, 1930 - Aug. 24, 1937
  - Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-278, pt. 1; Feb. 13, 1928 - Oct. 12, 1928
  - Gulf Coast Lines Railroad, 1926-1934 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-279; Jul. 20, 1926 - Jul. 11, 1934
  - Missouri and North Arkansas Railroad, 1926-1935 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-280; Aug. 16, 1926 - Apr. 29, 1935
  - Louisville, Henderson and St. Louis Railroad, 1926-1933 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-281; Dec. 2, 1926 - Aug. 30, 1933
  - Chicago and Illinois Midland Railroad, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-282; Jan. 20, 1927 - Feb. 10, 1927
  - Chicago Heights Terminal Transfer Railroad, 1927-1948 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-283; Feb. 7, 1927 - Oct. 15, 1948
  - Pacific Fruit Express Railroad, 1927-1937 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-284; Mar. 9, 1927 - Feb. 25, 1937
  - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad, 1927-1934 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-285; Apr. 5, 1927 - Feb. 25, 1937
  - Piedmont and Northern Railroad, 1928-1934 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Code No. 8-286; May 12, 1928 - Sept. 24, 1934
  - Chicago Junction Railway, 1931-1940 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Code No. 8-287; Oct. 28, 1931 - Jul. 6, 1940
  - Gulf and Ship Island Railroad, 1923-1925 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Code No. 8-288; Jun. 4, 1923 - Jun. 16, 1925
  - Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad, 1929-1934 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Code No. 8-290; Oct. 17, 1929 - Jul. 2, 1934
  - Southern Railroad, 1929-1933 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Code No. 8-291; Dec. 13, 1929 - Dec. 13, 1933
  - High Point Thomasville and Denton Railroad, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Code No. 8-293; Apr. 6, 1930 - May 13, 1930
  - East Tennessee and Western North Carolina Railroad, 1930-1941 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Code No. 8-294; Sept. 26, 1930 - Jul. 24, 1941
  - Cincinnati Union Terminal Railroad, 1932-1934 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Code No. 8-295; Dec. 30, 1932 - Sept. 25, 1934
  - Toronto, Hamilton and Buffalo Railroad, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Code No. 8-296; Dec. 11, 1930
  - Birmingham and Northwestern Railway, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Code No. 8-298; May 5, 1923 - Oct. 30, 1923
  - Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    Code No. 8-299; Oct. 25, 1934
  - Carolina, Clinchfield and Ohio Railroad, 1926-1934 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Code No. 8-300; Dec. 1, 1926 - Mar. 26, 1934
  - Cadsden Car Works, 1923-1929 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    Code No. 8-303; Jun. 4, 1923 - Aug. 29, 1929
  - Utah Railroad, 1923-1936 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    Code No. 8-305; May 19, 1923 - Sept. 8, 1936
  - St. Paul Bridge and Terminal Railroad, 1923-1936 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Code No. 8-306; Jun. 21, 1923 - Jun. 1, 1936
  - Mississippi Central Railroad, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    Code No. 8-307; Jul. 26, 1939 - Jul. 31, 1939
  - Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad, 1934-1945 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    Code No. 8-308; Aug. 21, 1934 - Feb. 8, 1945
  - Buffalo and Susquehanna Railroad, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Code No. 8-309; Oct. 7, 1931 - Nov. 12, 1931
  - Lakeside and Marblehead Railroad, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Code No. 8-310; Nov. 28, 1931 - Dec. 5, 1931
  - Pittsburgh, Shawmut and Northern Railroad, 1931-1942 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    Code No. 8-311; Dec. 2, 1931 - Jul. 20, 1942
  - Minneapolis, Northfield and Southern Railroad, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    Code No. 8-312; Dec. 9, 1931
  - Arkansas, Louisiana and Missouri Railroad, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Code No. 8-313; May 22, 1936
  - Monongahela Railway, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Code No. 8-315; Jul. 19, 1933 - Apr. 3, 1935
  - Merchants Dispatch Transportation Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Code No. 8-317; Aug. 9, 1933 - Oct. 5, 1934
  - Pacific Electric Railway, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Code No. 8-318; Aug. 28, 1933 - May 17, 1934
  - Ryan Car Co., 1933 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    Code No. 8-319; Aug. 31, 1933
  - Laramie, North Park and Western Railroad, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Code No. 8-320; Aug. 25, 1933 - Sept. 1, 1933
  - Ft. Worth Joint Car Inspectors Association, 1933-1936 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    Code No. 8-321; Aug. 30, 1933 - Jun. 5, 1936
  - Union Terminal of Kansas, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    Code No. 8-322; Sept. 26, 1933 - Jun. 2, 1935
  - New Orleans Terminal, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    Code No. 8-323; Sept. 27, 1933 - May 27, 1935
  - Dallas Car Interchange and Inspection Bureau, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    Code No. 8-324; Sept. 18, 1933 - May 27, 1935
  - Railway Express Agency, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    Code No. 8-325; Sept. 30, 1933 - Oct. 24, 1934
  - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    Code No. 8-326; Oct. 10, 1933
  - Illinois Terminal Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    Code No. 8-328; Oct. 27, 1933 - Mar. 27, 1934
  - Inter State Railroad, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    Code No. 8-329; Oct. 30, 1933 - Nov. 13, 1933
  - Louisiana and Arkansas Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    Code No. 8-331; Nov. 15, 1933 - Sept. 4, 1934
  - Union Belt Railway of Detroit, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    Code No. 8-332; Dec. 6, 1933 - Jul. 18, 1934
  - Detroit Union Railroad Depot and Station Co., 1933 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    Code No. 8-333; Dec. 6, 1933 - Dec. 18, 1933
  - Empty Folder (Box 12, Folder 52)
    Code No. 8-334
  - Manufacturers' Junction Railroad, 1933-1942 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    Code No. 8-335; Dec. 26, 1933 - Jun. 5, 1942
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    Code No. 8-335-23; Nov. 23, 1940
- Series IV a: International Organizations, American Federation of Labor - Union Affiliated with the AFL, 1912-1961
  Chiefly correspondence (carbons and originals), agreements, reports, and documents concerning agreement revisions, jurisdictional disputes, classification of work rules, organizing work, representational disputes, strikes called on various railroads, and
  - Boilermakers, 1937-1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Code No. 16-9, pt. 2; May 11, 1937 - Nov. 30, 1955; See also box 158
  - Electrical Workers, 1928-1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Code No. 16-15, pt. 1; Dec. 12, 1928 - May 28, 1945; See also box 158
  - Maintenance of Way Employees, 1912-1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Code No. 16-18, pt. 1; Dec. 12, 1912 - May 15, 1961; See also box 158
- Series Va: American Federation of Labor, Departments Other Than This Department and State Federations of Labor, 1941-1968
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), reports (many financial), agreements, and case files chiefly reflecting the merger of the AFL and CIO and its post merger activities. Also, materials dealing with the 1946 suspension of the International Association
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1941-1951 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 4; Aug. 21, 1941 - Feb. 15, 1951
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1952-1955 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 5; Apr. 10, 1952 - Apr. 31, 1955
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1955-1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 6; Oct. 10, 1955 - Jul. 10, 1957
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 7; Aug. 1957 - Dec. 24, 1957
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 8; Nov. 14, 1957 - Apr. 29, 1959
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 9; Apr. 23-24, 1959 - Dec. 16, 1960; See also box 158 and 159
  - Reports to and from the AFL, 1942-1960 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Code No. 17-2, pt. 3; Feb. 2, 1942 - Mar. 2, 1960
- Series VI: Railroad Employees' Department Credentials, 1934-1938
  Letters verifying employees name and address for voting; letters announcing election of new officers; letters presenting yearly issuance of RED credential cards (authorizing person to officially represent RED, and authorizing representation of authority i
  - Railroad Employees' Department Credentials, 1934-1938 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Code No. 19-7, pt. 2; Oct. 27, 1934 - Oct. 27, 1938
- Series VII a: American Federation of Railway Workers and Other Outside Organizations - Not Affiliated with the American Federation of Labor, 1927-1953
  Includes correspondence (carbons and originals), organizing materials, minutes, financial records, constitutions and by-laws, union generated promotional materials and reports concerning the attempts of twenty-nine unions to organize various groups of rai
  - American Federation of Railway Workers, 1938-1953 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Code No. 20-13, pt. 4; Aug. 12, 1938 - Nov. 24, 1953
  - American Federation of Railway Workers, 1940-1944 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Code No. 20-14; Aug. 28, 1940 - Jun. 15, 1944
  - United Welders of America, etc., 1927-1938 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Code No. 20-27; Jul. 29, 1927 - Aug. 3, 1938
  - Canadian Brotherhood, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Code No. 20-28, pt. 2; May 5, 1941
  - Niagara Frontier Association, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Code No. 20-31; Sept. 1, 1930 - Nov. 7, 1930
  - Tramp Veterans of the Rail, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Code No. 20-32; Jul. 6, 1932 - Aug. 29, 1932
  - American Railway Supervisors Association, 1934-1942 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Code No. 20-33, pt. 2; Nov. 21, 1934 - Dec. 16, 1943; See also box 159
  - Progressive Railway Union, 1934-1935 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Code No. 20-34; Dec. 28, 1934 - Mar. 4, 1935
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Shop Crafts of America, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Code No. 20-35, pt. 1; Sept. 17, 1934
  - McConnell Bill, 1937-1951 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Code No. 20-35; Apr. 8, 1937 - Dec. 5, 1951
  - District 50, United Mine Workers of America, 1942-1943 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Code No. 20-40; Nov. 25, 1942 - Nov. 1, 1943
  - Conference with the CIO RE: East and New England, 1941-1947 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Code No. 20-40-E. Reg., pt. 1; Jun. 2, 1941 - Mar. 20, 1947
  - CIO Activities, 1942-1950 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Code No. 20-40, pt. 4; Nov. 24, 1942 - Nov. 13, 1950
  - Railroad Brotherhoods and Auxiliaries Associations - Pensions, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Code No. 20-41; Nov. 12, 1937
  - Mutual Transportation Comm. Of Georgia, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Code No. 20-43; Dec. 22, 1939 - May 13, 1940
  - Railway Employees' Union Labor Club of Illinois, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Code No. 20-44; Sept. 30, 1940 - Oct. 11, 1940
  - Trainmen, Brakemen and Porters Union (Black), 1938 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Code No. 20-45; Sept. 23, 1938 - Dec. 12, 1938
  - Employees Joint Council in State of Utah, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Code No. 20-46, pt. 1; Jul. 11, 1940 - Apr. 1, 1941
  - Labor Journal, Inc., 1941-1944 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Code No. 20-48, pt. 1; Mar. 24, 1941 - Dec. 19, 1944
  - Southern Pacific Co., Minute Men's Association, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Code No. 20-49; Mar. 24, 1941
  - Telegraph Workers Independent Union, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Code No. 20-50; Jul. 21, 1941
  - Citizens Committee for Industrial Americanism, Inc., 1941 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Code No. 20-51; Dec. 1, 1941
  - American Railroad Foremen's Assoc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Code No. 20-52; May 25, 1942 - Sept. 11, 1942
  - Confederated Unions of America, 1942-1944 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Code No. 20-54; Jul. 9, 1942 - May 10, 1944
  - CUA News, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Code No. 20-54; May 1943 - Aug. 1944
  - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Code No. 20-55; Feb. 22, 1943 - Jun. 1, 1943